谢尔顿  现在打来真不是时候
Sheldon, it's not a great time!
你有啥事
What do you want?
我也跟你"问声好"啊
Hello to you, too.
抱歉  但这事很重要
I'm sorry, but this is important.
什么事
What is it?
《回到未来》第二部光盘被放到
Back to the Future II was
《回到未来》第三部的盒子里了
in the Back to the Future III case...
而《回到未来》第三部  你猜怎么着
and Back to the Future III was-- get this--
被放在了第二部的盒子里了
in the Back to the Future II case.
所以呢
So?
所以是你干的吗
So, did you do that,
还是我住的房子里有个入侵者
or am I in the house with an intruder?
谢尔顿  我要先进船舱了
Sheldon, I got to go inside.
外头风浪太大了
It's getting rough out here.
你在闪避问题
You're dodging the question;
我就知道是你干的
I knew it was you.
那是什么声音
What was that?
什么什么声音
What was what?
信号不是太好
This isn't a very good connection,
但感觉像海怪被释放出来了
but it sounded like someone just released a kraken.
好了  我要挂电话了
Okay, I'm hanging up now.
你知道世界上没有海...
You know there's no such thing as a...
别啊
No...!
佩妮  佩妮
Penny... Penny...
佩妮
Penny...!
怎么了
What's the matter?
我刚刚有点担心
Um... well, I was worried
你会很想念莱纳德
that you might be missing Leonard.
然后会害你做恶梦
And that might be causing you to have bad dreams,
就是那种睡前看了
like the kind you'd get if you watched
《诸神之战》之类的电影会做的恶梦
Clash of the Titans right before you went to bed.
亲爱的  是不是你做恶梦了啦
Sweetie, did you have a bad dream?
老实说  是的
To be honest, I did.
《回到未来》第二部光盘
Back to the Future II was
被放进第三部的盒子里
in the Back to the Future III case.
莱纳德干的
Leonard did it.
晚安
Good night.
等等
No, wait.
我是不是应该睡在这边
Perhaps I should sleep here
这样你不会太想念莱纳德
so you don't miss Leonard as much,
因为你现在就跟小孩一样楚楚可怜
uh, 'cause you're being kind of a baby about it.
好好好  你待着会让我舒服很多
You know what? That would make me feel better.
-谢谢你啊  -不用客气
- Thank you. - You're welcome.
晚安
Good night.
人人影视
YYeTs.com
生活大爆炸
第七季  第一集
你应该会很高兴听到这事
I think you'd be pleased to hear
今早我在停车场时
that this morning in the parking garage,
看到地上有一滩汽油渍
I saw this oil stain on the ground
形状就跟我前女友露西一模一样
that was shaped just like my ex-girlfriend, Lucy,
但我心情完全没受影响
and I didn't get upset at all.
我为你感到骄傲
I'm proud of you.
应该的  她看起来真是美爆了
Well, you should be, 'cause she was looking good.
我的老天爷啊  你是个天文学家
Dear Lord! You're an astronomer.
虽然你也有着人世间的烦恼
Although you may have earthly woes,
但你的脑子得想着天上繁星啊
get your mind back on the stars.
就连低等生物屎壳郎
Gee, even the lowly dung beetle
推粪的路线  都是以银河繁星作为指引
chooses to plot its course by using the Milky Way.
真的吗
Is that true?
我说的一切都是真的
Everything I say is true.
当然啦  屎壳郎也喜欢
Now, of course, the dung beetle also enjoys
食粪  住粪里
eating feces, living in feces
然后把粪便做成球
and making little balls out of feces.
自己选择
So pick and choose
要学习它生活中的哪些部分吧
which aspects of its lifestyle you want to embrace.
你现在都能正常跟女人说话了
Come on, you can talk to girls now.
再认识个新妞不难吧
It shouldn't be hard for you to meet someone new.
我怎么认识啊
How can I meet someone new
我现在看哪都能联想到露西的脸
when everywhere I look, I see Lucy's face?
你看这个鸡肉派的外皮
Tell me you don't see her smile
你能否认没看到她那笑容吗
in the crust of this chicken pot pie.
不许再犯傻了
Oh, will you stop it!
听好了
Now, listen to me.
今天晚上有一场博士后新生欢迎会
There's a welcome party for incoming post-docs tonight.
去参加  然后认识个
Go to it and meet someone
不是油渍或派做成的妹子
who isn't made of grease or pie.
怎么  你老婆是真人你就觉得自己牛逼啦
You think you're so cool because your wife is a person?
其实呢
Look,
妮妮与艾米去参加神经科学大会了
Bernie's at a neuroscience conference with Amy--
我陪你去吧
I'll go with you.
-你愿意为我这么牺牲吗  -当然
- You would do that for me? - Of course.
你是我朋友
You're my friend.
我也想你开心起来
I want you to be happy.
-谢了  -谢尔顿
- Thanks. - Oh, Sheldon,
既然艾米也不在  你要一起来吗
since Amy's out of town, would you like to join us?
我也想你开心
I want you to be happy, too,
但还没想到愿意付出实际行动
but not enough to do anything about it.
华仔别闹了
Howie, stop.
我不能说那种"话"
I can't talk like that.
艾米在旁边呢
Amy's right here.
谢尔顿别闹了  我最后一次保证
Sheldon, stop. For the last time,
我不会带着床虱回去的
I will not bring home bed bugs.
酒店很好
The hotel's nice.
有泳池  健身房
There's a pool, a gym--
酒吧感觉也挺好玩的
the bar looks like fun.
因为我检查过床了  没有床虱
Because I looked in the bed, and there are no bugs.
我也爱你
Aw, I love you, too.
如果你睡前没跟你说到话
If I don't talk to you before you go to sleep,
那我们就梦乡里相会吧
I'll meet you in dreamland.
晚安
Good night.
不  我不会考虑套着衣服保护套睡的
No, I will not consider sleeping in my garment bag.
佩妮  你好奇过  星际舰队战舰指挥官们...
Penny, did you ever wonder how Starfleet captains...
没有
No.
现在我已经激起了你的兴致
Well, now that I've piqued your interest,
欢迎来到刺激的3D象棋世界吧
welcome to the exciting world of 3D chess.
你为什么不老实说
Why don't you just admit
你想玩这个游戏
you only want to play this game
是因为你以前老跟莱纳德玩
because you always play it with Leonard
你很想念他
and you miss him?
你太高估了他对我生活的重要性
You overestimate his significance in my life.
我会想念他用糖浆
Do I miss how he makes a face
在我的松饼上画张脸吗
on my toaster waffle with syrup?
不会
No.
我会想念
Do I miss the way
他把我卡住的夹克拉链修好的方式吗
he fixes the zipper on my jacket when it gets stuck?
我想不会
I don't think so.
我会想念我们
Do I miss how we say "good night"
隔着卧室墙  用莫尔斯电报密码
to each other through the walls of our bedroom
互道晚安的夜晚吗
using Morse code?
好了  我懂了  我懂了
Okay, I get it, I get it.
你是个没有感情的机器人
You are an emotionless robot.
我尽量保持了
Well, I try.
好啦  赶紧把这破游戏玩完吧
All right, let's just get this stupid game over with.
-好的  我先走  -行
- Great. I'll go first. - Okay.
对了  你懂拉链吗
By the way, how are you with zippers?
怎么了
Why?
我真的得去上厕所了
Well, I really need to go to the bathroom,
可是这个拉链要整死我了
and this one's gone all cattywampus.
你的水母神经网络研究
Wow, your work on jellyfish neural nets
听起来蛮有意思的
sounds so interesting.
的确
It is.
你可以在学校伺服器上下到我的研究报告
You can download my paper off the university server.
会的  你也可以在学校伺服器上
I will. You can download my paper
下到我的范艾伦辐射带研究报告
on the Van Allen Belts from the university server as well.
会的
I will.
好的
All right.
怎么样了
How'd it go?
如果你喜欢无趣与论述事实
Well, if you like dry, factual statements
外加各种蛋疼的无语时分的交谈
interspersed with painful moments of silence,
那就绝对是爽歪歪了
it was bananas.
看那边
Check it out.
人力资源部的戴维斯女士也在
Mrs. Davis from Human Resources is here.
估计是来盯着有没有性骚扰案件的
She's probably on the lookout for sexual harassment.
漂亮
Oh, great.
这下我被人性骚扰的机会也飞了
There go my chances of being sexually harassed.
听说她老公泡了性感年轻女大生  甩了她
I heard her husband left her for a hot, young undergrad.
的确是比那个老丑货好超多啊
That's so much better than the old, ugly ones.
沃罗威茨先生
Mr. Wolowitz,
库萨帕里博士
Dr. Koothrappali.
戴维斯女士  你也好
Mrs. Davis, nice to see you.
我最近刚阅读了一篇有关企鹅中
You know, I recently read a fascinating article
也有雄性出轨情况的文章
on infidelity among penguins.
好的
Okay.
所以你老公离开你的这事
So if the fact that your husband left you
可能让你觉得自己年老色衰  但请想想
makes you feel unattractive, just remember,
连企鹅这么超可爱还会被雄性骗呢
penguins get cheated on, and they're adorable.
我宁愿你不能跟女人说话
It was better when you couldn't talk to women.
我打算去听听那场
I was thinking of going to the lecture
后扣带回皮质损伤
on posterior cingulate cortex lesions
对自传体记忆的形成课程
in the formation of autobiographical memory.
大脑损伤是很有意思啊
Oh, brain lesions are fascinating.
但如果是你的脑子  那就倒霉了
Unless they're yours, then they're a drag.
敬科学进步一杯
To the advancement of science.
也敬成就了这些的病人和死人
And to the sick and dying who make it possible.
这真不错  佩妮在的时候
This is fun; we never really get to talk shop
我们从没机会谈正事
with Penny around.
到最后都是在谈男人的事
We usually just end up talking about boys.
是也没关系啦  但偶尔能聊点
Which is fine, but it's nice to mix it up
高智商的东西也不错
with a little intellectual conversation.
吧台边的两位男士请的
From the two gentlemen at the bar.
天啊  有男生请我们喝酒
Oh, my gosh, boys bought us drinks!
男生请我们喝酒
Boys bought us drinks!
谢谢  谢谢  太谢谢了
Thank you, thank you, thank you so much.
-冷静  -冷静什么
- Be cool. - You be cool!
他们不是为了泡佩妮  才来泡我们的呢
Guys are hitting on us, and not just to get to Penny.
你说的有道理
You're right.
谢谢啊
Thank you.
坏棋啊
Bad move.
真的吗  为什么
Really? Why?
我的王后可以从下面吃掉你的车
My queen can now take your rook from below.
也就表示我输了  对吧
So that means I lose, right?
结束啦
It's over!
如果我下这步才会
If I make this move...
但我不会  因为我们玩得正开心呢
but I won't because we're having too much fun.
好吧  先休息一下
Okay, let's take a break.
我们家没酒了
We're all out of alcohol.
我不是要去拿酒好吗
I wasn't going to get alcohol.
天啊  我好想知道莱纳德现在在干嘛
Gosh, I wonder what Leonard's doing right now.
我好想他
I miss him so much.
你要是想
Well, if you'd like,
我们可以打给他啊
we could call him.
我是说  你可以打给他
I-I mean that you could call him.
我已经说过
As I've explained,
我的朋友不在  对我完全没影响
the absence of my friends does not cause me pain.
就如同摇滚坏男孩  保罗·西蒙唱过的
As rock and roll bad boy, Paul Simon, once said,
"我是一颗石头
"I am a rock.
我是一座孤岛"
I am an I-I-I-island."
我打给他吧
I'm calling him.
太棒了  记得开免提啊
Oh, goodie! Put him on speakerphone!
女士们  抱歉
Excuse me, ladies,
我的裤子在震动
but my pants are buzzing.
北海  有何能为你海带[音似效劳]
North Sea, how can I "Kelp" You?
莱纳德
Leonard?
佩妮
Penny?
是佩妮
Hey, it's Penny.
大家跟佩妮问声好吧
Everybody say hi to Penny.
你好  佩妮
Hi, Penny!
听起来你玩得挺开心的嘛
Wow, it sounds like you're having a good time.
这辈子最爽的时刻了
Best time of my life!
现在不是你们那边的凌晨五点半吗
Isn't it 5:30 in the morning there?
是吗
Is it?
各位  现在都凌晨五点半啦
Hey, everybody, it's 5:30 in the morning!
我们打给你
okay, well, we were just calling you
是因为我们想你了
because we were missing you.
-冰山  -等一下
- Iceberg! - Uh-oh, hang on.
你们是不是遇到危险了
Are you in danger?
不是啦  是喝酒游戏
No, it's a drinking game.
每次我们看见冰山的时候  都会干一杯
Whenever we see an iceberg, we take a shot!
冰山  冰山
Berg! Berg!
冰山  冰山  冰山  冰山
Berg! Berg! Berg! Berg--
莱纳德  莱纳德
Leonard, Leonard?
真不敢相信我们居然想念那个混蛋
I cannot believe we were missing that jerk.
是你而已
You were.
什么情况  进展如何
So what happened? How'd it go?
很好  我再次感谢他们
It's fine. I thanked them again
并告诉他们我们名花有主了
and let them know we're not available.
那就是说我不用为了这杯酒
So I can drink this without having
牺牲色相吗
to give up the goodies?
对  你就喝吧
Yes, it's all cool.
不过如果你想跟他们说话
Although, if you wanted to talk to one of them,
也没人会怪你的
no one would blame you.
为什么没人会怪我
And why would no one blame me?
我只是在随便乱说而已
I don't know what I'm saying.
貌似你是在说
Well, it sounds like you're saying
我可以找一个比谢尔顿更好的男友
that I could do better than Sheldon.
天啊  这杯酒真够劲儿啊
Boy, these drinks are strong!
妈呀  我今晚估计得抱着马桶吐了
Hoo, mama, I'm gonna be hug in the toilet tonight!
告诉我
No, tell me,
我想知道你那句话到底是什么意思
I want to know what you meant by that.
我只是说你还没结婚
I just meant that you're not married
而且你的男朋友有点...
and your boyfriend's kind of...
"谢尔顿"
Sheldon.
你的老公还很"霍华德"那型呢
And your husband is extremely Howard.
你是啥意思呢
What's your point?
抱歉  我没没啥意思
Sorry. I have no point.
刚才是我犯傻乱说话了
That was a stupid thing to say.
我们能不能既往不咎  回归原样呢
Can we please just go back to having a nice time?
本来是可以  但遗憾的是
We could, but unfortunately my brain is lesion-free
我的脑子没病
and I remember that rotten thing
清楚的记得你说我小宝贝的坏话呢
you just said about my sweet baboo.
别这样嘛  我道歉
Come on. I apologize.
能不能别追究了
Can we please just let it go?
-好吧  -谢谢
- Sure. - Thanks.
你老公是个怪胎  他的衣着超级可笑
Your husband's weird and his clothes are ridiculous.
真是气死我了
I can't believe it!
这段时间我茶不思饭不想
All this time I've been doing nothing
就光想着那个混蛋了
but sit around and miss that guy.
你知道最糟糕的是什么吗
And you know what the worst part is?
你得在没有伏特加酒的情况下
That you're having to process
处理你痛苦的情绪
your emotional pain without vodka?
才不是呢
No.
好啦  被你说中了
Yes.
但你知道第二糟糕的是什么吗
But you know what the second-worst part is?
他一点都不想我
He does not miss me at all.
让我来安慰你吧
Allow me to comfort you.
至少你现在健康地活着
At least you've got your health.
不是吧  就这样  这也叫安慰人呀
Really? Tha-That's it? That's comforting?
一百年以后
Um, uh, in a hundred years,
你俩都会死  这事不就无所谓了吗
you'll both be dead and it won't matter?
去死吧  拜托
No! Come on!
你应该说  "他当然想你啦"
You're supposed to say, "Of course he misses you.
"他是在用狂欢来掩盖内心的忧伤"
The only reason he's partying is to cover up his pain."
不  我一点都不这么觉得
Oh, no, I don't think that's true at all.
这也太荒谬了
This is ridiculous.
为什么我会因为他过得开心而郁闷呀
Why am I upset just because he's off having a good time?
可能你像疯子一样想象着
Well... perhaps you're obsessively picturing him
他跟另外一个女人酒后乱性
engaged in drunken coitus with another woman.
是这样吗  被我说中了吗
Is that it? Did I get it right?
好吧  谢谢你
Okay, tha-that's great.
你可以不用再安慰我了
You can stop trying to make me feel better now.
但是不行
Actually, I can't.
莱纳德走之前
Before Leonard left,
他让我答应他  一定要好好照顾你
he made me promise that I'd take care of you.
-真的吗  -真的
- He did? - Yes.
真是太贴心了
Oh, that's really sweet.
而且如果我做得好的话
Plus, if I do a good job,
他说回来时会送我一顶水手帽
he said he'd bring me back a sailor's cap.
现在我更想念他了
Now I miss him even more.
如果能安慰到你的话
Well, if it's any consolation,
我保证莱纳德离开你温暖的怀抱
I'm sure Leonard's tormented every moment
和诱人的嘴唇的每一秒  都饱受煎熬
he's away from your warm embrace and cherry lips.
谢谢你
Thanks.
你还真信呀
Oh, seriously?
打扰了  戴维斯女士
Uh, excuse me, Mrs. Davis?
干嘛
What?
抱歉我在你面前哪壶不开提哪壶
I'd like to apologize for being insensitive.
还把胸企鹅说得全都是混蛋一样
And for possibly making penguins seem like jerks,
因为他们百分之99都是好男人
'cause 99% of them are stand-up guys.
算了吧
Forget about it.
其实我和你
You know, you-you and I,
咱俩有很多共同之处
you and I have a lot in common.
是吗
Is that right?
是呀  我也是
Oh, yes, I-I, too,
在经历心碎的痛苦
am in the throes of heartbreak.
好吧  我把来龙去脉告诉你
Okay, fine, I'll tell you about it.
这杯热饮是安慰你的
Here is a hot beverage to comfort you.
用的是外带的杯子
It's in a to-go cup.
里面装的是"赶紧走"的饮料
Make of that what you will.
拜托  现在还早呢
Come on. It's still early.
我们来干点什么吧
Let's do something.
我一直在试图创造怎么玩4D象棋呢
Well, I have been toying around with an idea for 4-D chess.
不如我们来聊聊吧
How about we just talk?
好吧
All right.
-在4D象棋...  -不谈这个
- In 4-D chess... - No.
来嘛  我们来聊聊彼此的生活
Come on, let's talk about our lives.
告诉我你一些我不知道的事情
Tell me something about you I don't know.
我有九条裤子
I own nine pairs of pants.
好吧  这算一个良好的开端
Okay, that-that's a good start,
但我想知道点更私密的事情
but I was thinking maybe something a little more personal.
我懂了
I see.
我有九条内裤
I own nine pairs of underpants.
不如我先说吧
How about I go first?
可我不想知道你有多少条内裤
But I don't want to know how many underpants you own.
但从你卧室的地上看起来
Although, based on the floor of your bedroom,
我猜有上千条吧
I'd say it's a thousand.
好吧  有件事是我不为人知的秘密
Okay, look, here's something people do not know about me.
我刚搬来洛杉矶的时候
When I first moved out to L.A.,
我在一个讲述杀手人猿的
I did a topless scene in a low-budget horror movie
低成本恐怖电影里裸上身
about a killer gorilla.
在那之后  我觉得很羞愧
After I did it, I felt so ashamed.
但谢天谢地  那电影从没上映
Thankfully, that thing never came out.
我看过
I've seen that.
真的  《杀人恶猿》
Yeah. Serial Apeist.
在我们遇见你那天  霍华德就在网上发现了
Howard found it online the day we met you.
天啊
Oh, God...
确切来说  是在你走出我们这扇门之后
And it was literally the moment you walked out the door.
但我了解你想知道的是多私密的事情
But I see the type of personal revelations you're going for.
好吧  有个秘密我本来想带进棺材的
Okay, here's one I thought I'd take to the grave.
不久前
A while back,
YouTube网站更改了用户界面
YouTube changed its user interface
本来是用星级来评价视频
from a star-based rating system
改成了点赞
to a thumbs-up rating system.
我告诉人们我无所谓
I tell people I'm okay with it,
但其实我很介意
but I'm really not.
这就是你的大秘密吗
That's your big revelation?
是的
Yes.
让我顿时如释重负呀
I feel ten pounds lighter.
好吧  算了
Okay, you know what?
我放弃了
I give up.
我回去睡觉了
I'm going to bed.
还有一件事你不知道
Here's something else you don't know about me:
你刚伤害了我的感情
you just hurt my feelings.
我刚做什么了
What did I do?
我对你敞开心扉分享秘密
I opened up and shared something
让我最郁闷不已的秘密
deeply upsetting to me,
而你却表现得好像不是什么大事
and you treated it as if it were nothing.
我是不觉得这是大事
I-I didn't think it was a big deal.
但对我来说是  这就是重点
It is to me; that's the point.
谢尔顿  你说得对
Sheldon, you are right.
真的很不对不起
I'm really sorry.
我不该那么做
I should've known better.
我接受你的道歉
Your apology is accepted.
谢谢
Thank you.
那来抱一个吧
How about a hug?
-还是真诚地握个手算了  -抱一个嘛
- How about a hearty handshake? - Come on.
现在我知道你当时
Now I know how you felt getting mauled
被性致勃勃大猩猩袭击的感觉了
by that sex-crazed gorilla.
晚安
Good night.
今晚有陌生人请咱们喝酒真是受宠若惊呀
It was rather flattering to have strangers send us drinks.
对呀  感觉真好
Yeah, that felt nice.
或许明天我们应该穿上性感点的裤子
Maybe tomorrow morning we put on some hot pants
看看会不会有人请咱们吃煎蛋饼
and see if we can score us some free omelets.
假设如果我们当时跟他们一起走
So, hypothetically, if-if we were to have gone with them,
你会选择跟哪个走
which one would you have picked?
我觉得我会选
I think I would have gone with
那个发型可笑的矮子
the short one with the goofy haircut.
正好  因为我喜欢又高又瘦那个
Oh, good, 'cause I liked the tall thin one.
他看起来很聪明  有些孤傲
He seemed intelligent, kind of a loner,
或许缺乏性经验
maybe a little sexually inexperienced,
可以让我好好给他上一两节课
like I'd have to teach him a thing or two.
我那个不是这样
Not my guy.
我发现他盯着我的胸部看
I caught him staring at my rack.
有人想知道我羊毛衫下
It'd be nice to be with a man
藏着什么的感觉真好
who wants to know what's underneath my cardigan.
对了  是另一件羊毛衫哦
FYI, it's another cardigan.
你那个色鬼矮子听起来像霍华德
Your short sexed-up guy kind of sounds like Howard.
你那个聪明的处男听起来像谢尔顿
Your brainy virgin kind of sounds like Sheldon.
-晚安  -晚安
- Good night. - Night.
好了  库萨帕里博士
All right, Dr. Koothrappali,
跟你聊得很开心
it's been nice talking to you,
但我得回家让我保姆下班了
but I need to go home and relieve my babysitter.
当然  我也懂当单亲父母的感受
Yeah, I can relate to being a single parent.
我有一只狗
I have a dog.
是呀  这两者是"一样"的啊
Yeah, it's exactly the same thing.
晚安
Good night.
戴维斯女士
Mrs. Davis...
我必须坦白
I, uh, I must confess,
我今晚来这里是抱着失败的心
I came here tonight in a futile attempt
企图勾搭上某个寂寞的博士后
to pick up some lonely postdoc,
但我却意外跟你进行了人类层面的交流
but instead I got to connect with you at a human level.
比我想象的夜晚好多了
That's a much better evening.
你是个很棒的人
You're a lovely person.
你是在试图勾搭我吗
Are you hitting on me?
不  不  那样太扯了
No, no, no, that would be crazy!
如果我是在勾搭你  你会知道
I mean, if I were hitting on you, you'd know it
因为你会觉得不舒服  还会为我感到悲哀
'cause you'd feel uncomfortable and a little sad for me.
你人真好
You're sweet.
晚安  库萨帕里博士
Good night, Dr. Koothrappali.
晚安
Good night.
看起来她接受了你的道歉
Looks like she accepted your apology.
不止呢
And then some.
我觉得我们有擦出火花
I think we had a moment.
拜托  你们才没有擦出火花
Oh, please, you did not have a moment.
谁死后把火花鉴定王之位传给你了吗
Who died and made you king of moments?
好吧  就算你们有擦出火花
Okay, fine. Let's say there was a moment.
-明明有  -明明没有
- There was. - There wasn't.
即使就算真的有
But... But even if there was,
你还想干嘛
what are you gonna do about it?
我会慢慢勾引她
I will slowly seduce her
直到她无法抗拒  上我的床
until she falls helpless into my bed,
渴求只有我能给她的欢愉
hungry for the pleasure only I can give her.
-所以就是没啥  -对  没啥
- So nothing. - No, not a thing.
我真高兴警察终于
I'm so glad the police finally caught
把那只基因突变的疯狂人猿抓住了
that psychotic genetically engineered ape.
我对天发誓  那就是我的女朋友
That is my girlfriend! I swear to God!
莱纳德  莱纳德  好样的
Leonard! Leonard! Leonard! Leonard!